Let's talk about the prerequisites.
You do not need to be a stock market expert to do well in this course.
The students from different backgrounds are welcome.
If you are new to finance, that is fine.
Many students become interested in finance after they start working with the data.
We'll use Python throughout the course.
Many assignments will require you to write code, test your work, debug problems.
We'll move at a steady pace, so you should be ready to practice.
We'll also use coding agents to help us write and improve code.
These tools can be very helpful, but you still need to understand the basics of coding to use them well.
At minimum, you should be familiar with Python basics such as functions, loops, conditionals, and basic data structures.
If Python is new to you, plan to spend extra time early in the course getting comfortable with it.
I have also added resources on the course website to help you get started.
The finance concepts will build over time, but strong programming skills will help you keep up from the beginning.