Our course has three main parts.
The first part is working with financial data in Python.
In this part, we'll learn how to read historical financial data into Python, organize it, manipulate it, and then analyze it.
We'll also use Python to visualize financial data so we can see patterns more clearly.
The second part is computational investing.
In this part, we'll study the methods and models used in data-driven investing.
We'll look at ideas used by hedge funds, investment banks, and trading teams to work with financial data and make investment decisions.
The third part is machine learning methods for trading.
In this final part, we will bring everything together.
We'll take the financial data skills from the first part, the investment concepts from the second part, and then apply machine learning methods to trading problems.
We'll use and discuss algorithms such as Random Forest and QLearning and we'll see how these tools can be used to build trading strategies.
My goal is that after you complete this course, you will be prepared to contribute to a trading system development team, such as at a hedge fund and investment bank or a financial technology company.
You should be able to work with financial data and you should be able to analyze them, build models, test ideas, and think carefully about the results.
At the same time, I want to be clear about one thing.
Completing this course does not mean you should immediately start automated trading with real money.
The course is a starting point.
It will give you the foundation to understand how these systems are built and what it takes to use them responsibly.