Hi everyone.
Welcome to Machine Learning in Finance.
My name is Asif Rasool and I will be your instructor for this course.
Let me start with a simple question.
Suppose I'm thinking about buying Apple stock.
Should I buy it?
The honest answer is it depends.
It depends on many things.
My answer depends on my portfolio, my risk tolerance, the information I have, my investment goal, or even my time horizon.
Am I investing for the short run?
Am I investing for the long run?
Or am I trying to build a trading strategy?
Questions like these are central to this course.
We will study how information influences stock prices, how to build software to analyze and visualize financial relationships, and how stock exchanges work.
Later in this course, we'll use machine learning algorithms to build trading strategies.
I had a lot of fun developing this course.
I hope you enjoy it too.
Let's get started.